RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 21. Official Statements, 1971-1975
  - Beauty Salon Week (Box A-928)
  - Beta Sigma Phi (Box A-928)
  - Bicentennial Celebration Day, Sacred Heart University, 1974 May 11 (Box A-928)
  - Bicentennial – Reactivation of Military Units, P.A. 73-220 (Box A-928)
  - Bicycle Safety Week (Box A-928)
  - Big Band Month (Box A-928)
  - Big Brothers (Torrington) (Box A-928)
  - Bill of Rights Day (Box A-928)
  - Black Expo 74 Week (Box A-928)
  - Black Teenage Pageant (Message) (Box A-928)
  - Blind – Braille Elevator Markings in Public Buildings (Box A-928)
  - B’nai B’rith – Aleph Zadik Aleph Youth Organization Month (Box A-928)
  - B’nai B’rith Month, 1973 October (Box A-928)
  - B’nai B’rith Career and Counseling Services (Box A-928)
  - B’nai B’rith “Let Our People Go” Month (Box A-928)
  - Boston Patriots (Message) (Box A-928)
  - Boys Club Week (Box A-928)
  - Boy Scout Month (Box A-928)
  - Breath of Life Week (Cystic Fibrosis) (Box A-928)
  - Bristol Boys Club (Message) (Box A-928)
  - Brotherhood in Action Sunday (Box A-928)
  - Business Education Day (Box A-928)
  - Business Women’s Week (Box A-928)
  - Byelorussian Independence Day (Box A-928)
  - Camp Fire Girls Week (Box A-928)
  - Cancer Control Month (Box A-928)
  - Cancer Education Week (Box A-928)
  - Captive Nations Week (Box A-928)
  - Care Week (Box A-928)
  - Carver, George Washington Day (Box A-928)
  - Catholic Daughters of America (Box A-928)
  - Central Connecticut State College, 125th Anniversary (Box A-928)
  - Cerebral Palsy Month (Box A-928)
  - Career Guidance Week (Box A-928)
  - Certified Engineering Technicians (Box A-928)
  - Catholic Schools Week, 1974 February (Box A-928)
  - Cheerleaders’ Week, 1974 August 4-9 (Box A-928)
  - Child Mental Health Week (Box A-928)
  - Children’s Dental Health Week (Box A-928)
  - Children’s Matinee Days (Box A-928)
  - China Information Week (Box A-928)
  - Christian Education Week (Box A-928)
  - Christmas, Keep Christ in (Box A-928)
  - Christmas Safety Program (Box A-928)
  - Christmas Seal Campaign, November 10-December 31 (Box A-928)
  - Circus in the Snow Newington Ski Club (Box A-928)
  - Citizenship Day and Constitution Week (Box A-928)
  - City of Hope Medical Center (Message) (Box A-928)
  - Civil Air Patrol (Box A-928)
  - Civil Preparedness (Box A-928)
  - Clean Air Week (Box A-929)
  - (National) Clean Up Month (September) (Box A-929)
  - Clown Week (Box A-929)
  - Coast Guard Day (Box A-929)
  - Colonial Bank and Trust (Box A-929)
  - Colchester – 275th Anniversary (Box A-929)
  - Columbian Squires Day (Box A-929)
  - Congressional Medal of Honor Day, 1974 June 24 (Box A-929)
  - Community Arts Council Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Air Nat’l Guard Day (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Conservation Convention (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Day Eastern States Exposition (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Highway Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Hospital Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Horse Show Days (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Humanities Council (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Inventors Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Nurse Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Opera Associations (30th Anniversary Message) (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Petroleum Assoc. (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Police Academy (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Public Television (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Purchasing Week (Box A-929)
  - Conn. State Elks Assoc. (Box A-929)
  - Conn. State Federation (Box A-929)
  - Conn. State Federation Women’s Clubs (Box A-929)
  - Conn. State Technical Colleges (Box A-929)
  - Conn. Yankee A.A.U. Swim Meet (Box A-929)
  - Constitution Week (Box A-929)
  - Consumer Information Week (Box A-929)
  - Cooley’s Anemia (Box A-929)
  - Copernicus Quintcentennial (Box A-929)
  - Country Music Month (Box A-929)
  - Crafts Month (Box A-929)
  - Danny Thomas Days (St. Jude) (Box A-929)
  - Day of Bread (Box A-929)
  - Defensive Driving Week (Box A-929)
  - DeMolay Week (Box A-929)
  - Dental Assistants (Box A-929)
  - Dental Disease Prevention (Box A-929)
  - Diabetes Detection Week (Box A-929)
  - Digestive Disease Month (Box A-929)
  - Distributive Education Week (Box A-929)
  - Drafting Week (Box A-929)
  - Drug Abuse Prevention Week (Box A-929)
  - Drug Bookmobile Information (Box A-929)
  - Drug Education Month (Box A-929)
  - Drum Corps Week (Box A-929)
  - Earth Week (Box A-929)
  - Easter Seal Campaign (Box A-929)
  - Edison Science Youth Day (Box A-929)
  - Education Week on Smoking (Box A-929)
  - Educational Secretaries Week (Box A-929)
  - Tribute to Duke Ellington (Box A-929)
  - Emblem Club Week (Box A-929)
  - Employ the Handicap Week (Box A-929)
  - National Engineers Week (Box A-929)
  - Epilepsy Month (Box A-929)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Day (Box A-929)
  - Equal Housing Opportunity (Box A-929)
  - Estonian Independence Day (Box A-929)
  - Executive House Keepers Week (Box A-929)
  - Eye Bank Month (Box A-929)
  - Family Doctor Week (Box A-929)
  - Family Reunion Day (Box A-929)
  - Family Week (Box A-929)
  - Farm Safety Week (Box A-929)
  - Father’s Day (Box A-929)
  - Favarh Horse Show Days (Box A-929)
  - Felician Order Nun 100th Anniversary (Box A-929)
  - Field Service Week (Box A-929)
  - Fire Prevention Week (Box A-929)
  - Flag Day (Box A-929)
  - Foot Health Week (Box A-929)
  - Foreign Language Week (Box A-929)
  - Forestry (Box A-929)
  - Foster Parents (Grand) Day (Box A-929)
  - Franco-American Day (Box A-929)
  - Freedom of Enterprise (Box A-929)
  - Free Cuba Day (Box A-929)
  - Future Business Leaders of America (Box A-929)
  - Future Farmers of America (Box A-929)
  - Gamma Sigma Sigma (Message) (Box A-930)
  - General Aviation Safety (Box A-930)
  - General Telephone (and) Electronics (Box A-930)
  - Girl Scout Week (Box A-930)
  - Greek Order – St. Dennis of Zante Day (Box A-930)
  - Greek Oxi Day (Box A-930)
  - Hadassah Month (Box A-930)
  - Hanukkah Message (Box A-930)
  - Hartt Opera-Theater Week (Box A-930)
  - Hartford Symphony Week (Box A-930)
  - Health Fair (Box A-930)
  - Hearing and Speech Month (May) (Box A-930)
  - Girls Club Week, 1974 May 12-18 (Box A-930)
  - Gold Star Mother’s Day (Box A-930)
  - Golden Jubilee Greek Orthodox (Box A-930)
  - Golf Day (Box A-930)
  - Golf Week in Connecticut (G.H.O.) (Box A-930)
  - Good Character Day, August 8 (Box A-930)
  - Gospel Music Week (Box A-930)
  - Grandparents Day (Box A-930)
  - Grange Week (Box A-930)
  - Great Trail Day (Box A-930)
  - Greek Independence Day (Box A-930)
  - Official Statements to be Indexed (Box A-930)
  - Heart Month (Box A-930)
  - Hebrew Academy of Greater Hartford (Box A-930)
  - Help Young America Campaign (Box A-930)
  - Hemophilia Month (Box A-930)
  - National Heritage Day (Box A-930)
  - High Blood Pressure Week, 1973 December 2-8 (Box A-930)
  - High School Coaches Week (Box A-930)
  - Highway Safety (message) (Box A-930)
  - Hire Deaf Mute Week (Box A-930)
  - Hire a Veteran Month (Box A-930)
  - Holy Ghost Fathers 100th Anniv. (Box A-930)
  - Honey Sunday Week (Box A-930)
  - Commodore Isaac Hull Day (Box A-930)
  - Human Growth Week (Box A-930)
  - Human Rights Day for Soviet Jewry (Box A-930)
  - Hungarian Freedom Fighters (Box A-930)
  - Hunting and Fishing Day (Box A-930)
  - Immunization Action Month (Box A-930)
  - India Republic Day (Box A-930)
  - Industrial Nurse Week (Box A-930)
  - Insurance Women’s Week (Box A-930)
  - International Air Cadet exchange (Box A-930)
  - Int’l DeMolay Week (Box A-930)
  - Int’l Longshoremen's Assoc. (Box A-930)
  - Int’l Walk for Development (Box A-930)
  - Irish Feisanna (Festival) (Box A-930)
  - Irish Heritage Week (Box A-930)
  - Israel, Full Support for, 1973 October 19 (Box A-930)
  - Israel, 25th Anniversary (Box A-930)
  - Charles E. Ives (centennial) (Box A-930)
  - Jaycee Week (Box A-930)
  - Jaycees Care Line Week (Box A-930)
  - Jaycees March for Olympics (Box A-930)
  - Jaycees / Look It and Pocket It The Key (Box A-930)
  - Jazz Week (Box A-930)
  - Jewish New Year (Box A-930)
  - Jewish War Veterans (Box A-930)
  - Jewish Welfare Board Basketball Weekend (Box A-930)
  - Nat’l Council Jewish Women (Box A-930)
  - Joy of Seeing Contest (Box A-930)
  - Junior Achievement Week (Box A-930)
  - Justice for Juvenile Day (Box A-930)
  - Karate Week, 1973 April 22-28 (Box A-930)
  - Keep America Beautiful (Box A-930)
  - Key Club Week (Box A-930)
  - Kidney Disease Advisory Committee (Box A-930)
  - Kidney Foundation Trick / Treat (Box A-930)
  - Knights of Columbus Founders Day (Box A-930)
  - Knights of Columbus / Month For Mentally Retarded (Box A-930)
  - Koufax / Mantle Baseball (Waterbury) (Box A-930)
  - Krayeske (and) McHugh (Box A-930)
  - Land Surveyors Week (Box A-931)
  - Latin Businessman & Industrialist (Box A-931)
  - Latvian Independence (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Law Day (Box A-931)
  - Law & Order Day (Box A-931)
  - Law Week, Respect for (Box A-931)
  - Learning Disabilities Week (Box A-931)
  - Legal Secretaries Week, 1973 October (Box A-931)
  - Letter Carrier Week, 1973 May 1-6 (Box A-931)
  - Leukemia – Lenny Eckstein Day, 1974 February 16 (Box A-931)
  - Leukemia Month (Box A-931)
  - Licensed Practical Nurse (Box A-931)
  - Life Insurance Week (Box A-931)
  - Lions Month (Box A-931)
  - Liquor Industry Day, 1973 December 5 (Box A-931)
  - Literacy Volunteer Week, 1974 September 23-29 (Box A-931)
  - Literacy Week (Box A-931)
  - Lithuanian Independence Day (Box A-931)
  - Long Wharf Theatre (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Loyalty Day (Conn. VFW) (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Manufacturing Engineers Day, Connecticut Society of (Box A-931)
  - March of Dimes Month (Box A-931)
  - Marine Corps Day (Box A-931)
  - Maritime Heritage Week, 1974 June 23-28 (Box A-931)
  - Marti, Jose Day (Cuba) (Box A-931)
  - Meals for Millions Month, November, 1973 (Box A-931)
  - Medic-Alert Month (Box A-931)
  - Medical Assistants Week (Box A-931)
  - Medical Society Woman’s Auxiliary, Connecticut State, 30th Anniversary, 1974 May 1 (Box A-931)
  - Medical Technology Week (Box A-931)
  - Memorial Day (Box A-931)
  - Men’s Garden Club Week (Box A-931)
  - Midget & Pony Football Week (Box A-931)
  - Milford Hospital (Message) (Box A-931)
  - MIA Awareness Day (Box A-931)
  - Monte Cassino, Battle of, 30th Anniversary, 1974 May 19 (Box A-931)
  - Month of Hope for Children (Box A-931)
  - Montville Center Congregational Church (Box A-931)
  - Moonwalk Week (Box A-931)
  - Moral Responsibility Weekend (Box A-931)
  - Morgan School Centennial (Box A-931)
  - Mother of the Year, Connecticut (Box A-931)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, Conquer (Box A-931)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Day/Month (Box A-931)
  - National Bible Week (Box A-931)
  - National Cancer Day (Box A-931)
  - National Education Week on Smoking (Box A-931)
  - National Federation for the Blind (Box A-931)
  - National Football Foundation & Hall of Fame (Box A-931)
  - National Action Foster Children (Box A-931)
  - National Freedom Day (Box A-931)
  - National Home Week (Box A-931)
  - National Maritime Day (Box A-931)
  - National Music Week (Box A-931)
  - National New Prosperity Week (Box A-931)
  - National Next Door Neighbor Day (Box A-931)
  - National OIC Day (Opportunities Industrialization Centers) (Box A-931)
  - National Parkinson Week (Box A-931)
  - National Parks Centennial (Box A-931)
  - National Pharmacy Week (Box A-931)
  - National Radio Month (Box A-931)
  - National Rife Association (Message), Wallingford (Box A-931)
  - National Salesman Week (Box A-931)
  - National Secretaries Week (Box A-931)
  - National Student Government Day (Box A-931)
  - National Transportation Week (Box A-931)
  - National Tree Appreciation Week (Box A-931)
  - National Volunteer Week (Box A-931)
  - National Wildlife Week (Box A-931)
  - Navy Day (Box A-931)
  - Navy Nurse Corps Week (Box A-931)
  - Negro History Week (Box A-931)
    See also African American History Week.
  - New England Numismatic (Message) (Box A-931)
  - New Horizons Week) (Box A-931)
  - Newspaper Carrier Day (Box A-931)
  - Nurse Anesthetist Week in Connecticut, 1974 September 29-October 5 (Box A-931)
  - Nursing Home Week (Box A-931)
  - Nutmeg Bowl Game (Box A-931)
  - Old Guard Day (Box A-931)
  - Opportunities In Connecticut Industry (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Orange Sesquicentennial Week (Box A-931)
  - Order of Women Legislators (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training Day (Box A-931)
  - ORLAT LWOW Cemetery Day (Box A-931)
  - Painting and Decorating Week (Box A-931)
  - Paralyzed Veterans of America (Message) (Box A-931)
  - Parent-Teacher Association Enrollment Month (Box A-931)
  - Parents Without Partners (Box A-931)
  - Passover – United Jewish Appeal (Box A-931)
  - Patriotic Education Week (Box A-931)
  - Patriots Day, 1974 April 19 (Box A-931)
  - Peace Corps – Vista (Box A-931)
  - Pershing Rifles Day (Box A-931)
  - Physical Education Week (Box A-931)
  - Physical Fitness for Elderly (Box A-931)
  - Physical Fitness Week (Box A-931)
  - Physical Therapy Week (Box A-931)
  - Pioneer Day (Box A-931)
  - Pitch, Hit & Throw. Major League Baseball (Box A-931)
  - Pitch In! Month (Keep Connecticut Clean) (Box A-931)
  - Plant Connecticut Week (Box A-931)
  - Plumbing Industry Week (Box A-931)
  - Poetry Day (Box A-931)
  - Poison Prevention Week (Box A-931)
  - Policemen and Firemen Week (Box A-932)
  - Polish American Congress “Events of August” (Message) (Box A-932)
  - Polish Constitution Day (Box A-932)
  - Polish Independence Day (Box A-932)
  - Polka Music Month (Box A-932)
  - Polonia Day USA (Box A-932)
  - Postal Service Day / Week (Box A-932)
  - Portland Ancient Muster (Box A-932)
  - Postal Clerks Week (Box A-932)
  - Pray for Peace Week (Box A-932)
  - Prayer for America (Nation) Day, 1973 November 4 (Box A-932)
  - Prayer Salute to Our Men in Vietnam (Box A-932)
  - Payer Vigil Week (Box A-932)
  - Prince Hall Week (Masons) (Box A-932)
  - Printing Week (Box A-932)
  - Prisoner of War Day (Box A-932)
  - Production and Inventory Control (Box A-932)
  - Puerto Rican Week (Box A-932)
  - Professional Photographer’s Week (Box A-932)
  - Public Service Weekend (TKE) (Box A-932)
  - Public Works Week (Box A-932)
  - Punt, Pass and Kick Day (Box A-932)
  - Putnam Phalanx (Message) (Box A-932)
  - Quality of Life Conference Day, 1974 April 27 (Box A-932)
  - Quality and Reliability Week (Box A-932)
  - Quarter Midget Racing (Box A-932)
  - Queen Isabella Day (Box A-932)
  - Racism – A decade for action to combat racism and racial discrimination, 1973 – 1983 (Box A-932)
  - Real Estate Boards (Message) (Box A-932)
  - Realtor Week (Box A-932)
  - Records Management Week (Box A-932)
  - Red Cross (Box A-932)
  - Refrigeration Safety Week (Box A-932)
  - Religious Overseas Aid Month (Box A-932)
  - Restaurant Month (Box A-932)
  - Retarded Children’s Month (Box A-932)
  - Retarded Citizens, Legal Rights for (Box A-932)
  - Retinitis Pigmentosa Day, 1973 October 28 (Box A-932)
  - Rid Litter Day (Box A-932)
  - Right to Read Month (Box A-932)
  - Rumanian Day (Tenth of May) (Box A-932)
  - Run for Freedom Day – POW/MIA, 1973 November 15 (Box A-932)
  - Safe Boating Week (Box A-932)
  - Safety on the Streets Week (Box A-932)
  - Safety Week, Connecticut (Box A-932)
  - Saint Joseph College Day (Box A-932)
  - St. Mary’s Parish, 100th Anniversary, East Hartford (Box A-932)
  - St. Patrick’s Day (Message) (Box A-932)
  - Salute to Avco (Blood Donors) (Box A-932)
  - Salute to Law Enforcement Agencies (Box A-932)
  - Salute to Will Rogers Research Center (Box A-932)
  - Salvation Army Week (Box A-932)
  - Santa Lucia Week (Box A-932)
  - Save Your Vision Week (Box A-932)
  - Savings Bond Month (Box A-932)
  - Saybrook Ancient Muster Day (Box A-932)
  - School Bus Safety Week (Box A-932)
  - School Nurses Week (Box A-932)
  - School Nutrition Week (Box A-932)
  - School Safety Patrol Day (Box A-932)
  - Science in Connecticut Day (Box A-932)
  - Senior Citizen’s Month (Box A-932)
  - Shad Derby Week (Box A-932)
  - Shakespeare at Home Day (Box A-932)
  - Share a Song Day (Sweet Adelines) (Box A-932)
  - Sight-saving Month (Box A-932)
  - Small Business Week (Box A-932)
  - Smoking – Rights of Non-Smoker, Connecticut Lung Association (Box A-932)
  - Softball (International) Week, 1974 August 8-16 (Box A-932)
  - Soil Stewardship Week (Box A-932)
  - Solidarity Day for Soviet Jews (Box A-932)
  - Southbury Tercentennial Week (Box A-932)
  - Space Week in Connecticut, 1973 (Box A-932)
  - Special Olympics Day (Box A-932)
  - Speech and Hearing Association, 25th Anniversary, 1974 (Box A-932)
  - Spring Clean-up Months (Box A-932)
  - Square Dance Week (Box A-932)
  - Stamp Week (Box A-932)
  - State Employee Week (Box A-932)
  - State Park Week (Box A-932)
  - Student Government Week (Box A-932)
  - Symphony Week (Box A-932)
  - Tall Cedars of Lebanon Week (Box A-932)
  - Toastmasters Month (Box A-932)
  - Toastmistress Month (Box A-932)
  - Traffic Safety Week (Box A-932)
  - Trauma Day (Box A-932)
  - Travelers Aid Week (Box A-932)
  - Trinity College, 150th Anniversary, 1973 May 16 (Box A-932)
  - Twain, Mark Centennial, 1974 September 12 (Box A-932)
  - Ukrainian Day of Mourning and Prayer (Box A-932)
  - Ukrainian Independence (Box A-932)
  - UNICO Mental Health Week (Box A-932)
  - UNICO National Founders Week (Box A-932)
  - Union Label Week (Box A-932)
  - United Nations Day (Box A-932)
  - U.S. Army Reserve Community Month (Box A-932)
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights (Box A-932)
  - Up with People (Box A-932)
  - Value Engineering Week (Box A-933)
  - Verrazano Day, 1974 April 17 (Box A-933)
  - Veterans Adm. Voluntary Service Week (Box A-933)
  - Veterans Foreign Wars (Message) (Box A-933)
  - Veterans Van Dedication Day, 1973 August 15 (Box A-933)
  - Vietnam Veterans Day (Box A-933)
  - Vocational Education Week (Box A-933)
  - Voice of Democracy Week (Box A-933)
  - Voter Registration Month (Box A-933)
  - Waterbury Tercentennial, 1974 (Box A-933)
  - Week of Concern for Americans who are Prisoners of War or Missing in Action, National (Box A-933)
  - Week of Concern for World Hunger (Box A-933)
  - Weights and Measures Week (Box A-933)
  - Welcome to Connecticut (Message, Hartford Courant) (Box A-933)
  - West Indian Week (Box A-933)
  - Whale, Connecticut Save the Days, 1974 May 2-3 (Box A-933)
  - Wolcott, 175th Anniversary (Message) (Box A-933)
  - Women’s Basketball Coaches Clinics, 1973 November 9 (Box A-933)
  - Women’s Civic Community Organization Month (Box A-933)
  - Women in Construction Week (Box A-933)
  - Women’s Week (Box A-933)
  - Work Incentive Program (WIN) Conference (Box A-933)
  - World Trade Week (Box A-933)
  - Yom Kippur (Box A-933)
  - Young Child, Week of the (Box A-933)
  - Youth Appreciation Week (Box A-933)
  - Youth Arts Month (Box A-933)
  - Youth Crusade Day (Box A-933)
  - Youth Temperance Education Week (Box A-933)
  - Zion Lutheran Church, 100th Anniversary, 1974 (Box A-933)
- Series 22. Papers of Task Force on Refineries, 1974-1975
  Correspondence, reports, questionnaires, working papers.
  - Records (Box A-934 - A-943)